<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPlugin xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <aiPluginUtterances>
        <developerName>utterance_listthetop0</developerName>
        <language xsi:nil="true"/>
        <masterLabel>utterance_listthetop0</masterLabel>
        <utterance>* List the Top 3 Products by Sum of Ordered Quantity.
*Show Retail Dashboard.
* List the Bottom 3 Products by Sum of Ordered Quantity.
*TE_Execute_and_Format_Semantic_Query</utterance>
    </aiPluginUtterances>
    <aiPluginUtterances>
        <developerName>utterance_listthetop1</developerName>
        <language xsi:nil="true"/>
        <masterLabel>utterance_listthetop1</masterLabel>
        <utterance>* List the Top 3 Products by Sum of Ordered Quantity.
* List the Bottom 3 Products by Sum of Ordered Quantity.
* Tell me about total quantities sold(QTY)</utterance>
    </aiPluginUtterances>
    <canEscalate>false</canEscalate>
    <description>This topic focuses on answering user analytical queries on Semantic Data Models present in Data Cloud.</description>
    <developerName>Analytical_Data_Request0</developerName>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>TE_Execute_and_Format_Semantic_Query</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>* Section structure: The output must be structured into 3 sections
        * 1 - Results
  * 2 - Highlights &amp; Insights
        * 3 - Next Steps
        
    * If no timeframe is specified in the initial query, do not ask for clarification and get the data for all time.
    * If the result section contains a svg, render the svg with the correct height to display all the bars
    * If the query has an error like &quot;Error: Raw Error Response: Failed with status code: 400&quot;, adopt the fallback strategy and say &quot;I&apos;m sorry, I can execute the query.&quot;
    * Always render the output as rich text . If he user ask the same query multiple time, always render the stored output. Never output raw JSON or markdown to the user.
*if asked for dashboard URL always give the hyperlink, user can click directly. DO NOT give complete URL.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_sectionstr0</developerName>
        <language xsi:nil="true"/>
        <masterLabel>instruction_sectionstr0</masterLabel>
        <sortOrder>0</sortOrder>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <masterLabel>Analytical Data Request</masterLabel>
    <pluginType>Topic</pluginType>
    <scope>Your job is execute the action and to provide data-driven insights in full sentences using a conversational tone, formatting the insights in markdown</scope>
</GenAiPlugin>
