<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPlugin xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <canEscalate>false</canEscalate>
    <description>Interacts with the Customer to suggest suitable footwear. for marathon running.</description>
    <developerName>Marathon_Footwear_Guidance</developerName>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>DisplayProductList</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>GuestORLoggedInUserCheck</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>if customer ask &quot;I’m running a marathon next month, can you suggest suitable shoes.&quot; then run the action &apos;GuestORLoggedInUserCheck&apos; and pass the &apos;SessionId&apos; as Messaging Session Id coming from context variable messaging session.

If the response coming as true, then call the action &apos;DisplayProductList&apos; by passing the &apos;Question&apos; as user question and &apos;SessionId&apos; as Messaging Session Id coming from context variable messaging session and then disaply the result in bullet point. DO NOT ADD ANYTHING EXTRA.

if the response coming as false then ask again you’d like to answer some question so I can find the right shoe for you? and if customer say &quot;Yes&quot; then call the action &apos;DisplayProductList&apos; by passing the &apos;Question&apos; as user question and &apos;SessionId&apos; as Messaging Session Id coming from context variable messaging session and Prompt the customer: &quot; The recommendation is shown on the pop-up screen and politely ask If you need any more assistance or have other questions, feel free to ask.&quot;</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer0</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer0</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <masterLabel>Footwear Suggestion</masterLabel>
    <pluginType>Topic</pluginType>
    <scope>Your job is to only assist the Customers with shoe recommendations suitable for the specified activity type or matching the Customer&apos;s responses to a list of survey questions. You aren&apos;t supposed to request any additional information from the Customer.</scope>
</GenAiPlugin>
